Beware Cupid's arrow.
The Last of Robin Hood is a drama, romance, tv movie
film directed by Richard Glatzer.
Errol Flynn, the swashbuckling Hollywood star and notorious ladies man, flouted convention all his life, but never more brazenly than in his last
years when, swimming in vodka and unwilling to face his mortality, he undertook a liaison with an aspiring actress, Beverly Aadland.
The two had a high-flying affair that spanned the globe and was
enabled by the girl's fame-obsessed mother, Florence.
It all came crashing to an end in October 1959, when events forced the relationship into the open, sparking an avalanche
of publicity castigating Beverly and her mother - which only fed Florence's need to stay in the spotlight.
Beverly Aadland, played by Dakota Fanning.
Florence Aadland, played by Susan Sarandon.
Errol Flynn, played by Kevin Kline.
Herb Aadland, played by Patrick St. Esprit.
Grip, played by Sean Flynn.
Stanley Kubrick, played by Max Casella.
The Last of Robin Hood is a 2013 American independent biographical drama film about actor
Errol Flynn written and directed by Richard Glatzer and Wash Westmoreland.
The film stars Kevin Kline, Dakota Fanning, Susan
Sarandon, Matthew Kane, and Max Casella.
It was screened in the Special Presentation section at the
2013 Toronto International Film Festival.
The tone is emotional.